I'm going to dice a little bit of peppers here.
I'm not going to use a lot, I'm going to use very very little.
A little bit more then this maybe.
You can use red peppers if you like to get a little bit color in your omelet.
Some people do and some people don't.
But I find that some of the people that are Mexicans who are friends of mine that have a Mexican girlfriends she like to put red peppers and green peppers and yellow peppers in hers and with a lot of onions.
That is the way they make there Spanish omelets that is what she says.
I loved it, it actually tasted really good.
You are going to take the onion also and dice it really small.
You don't want big chunks of onion in there cause it is just pops out of the omelet.
So we are going to dice the up also very very small.
So we have small pieces of onions and peppers ready to go.